http://www.401khelpcenter.com/privacy.html

401khelpcenter.com Website Privacy Statement
This privacy statement has been created to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:
General
The privacy of our users is of utmost importance to us. In general,
You do not have to give us personal information to visit our site, but be sure you review our Terms of Use.
We will collect personally identifiable information (email address) only if specifically and knowingly provided by you.
Personally identifying information you provide will be used only in connection with our services or for such other purposes as described at the point of collection.
We do not sell any personal information to third-parties.
We may enable "cookies." A "cookie" is a file placed on your personal computer's hard drive by a website that allows it to monitor your use of this site.
We do not track users over time and across third-party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third-party sites used by us may keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you.
We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 years of age.
eNewsletter
Our eNewsletter registration process ask users to give us contact information (e.g., name, email). Demographic data may also be collected at our site. This information may be shared with advertisers. We do not SPAM or support the practice.
Advertisers and Cookies
We may use a number of outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads often contain cookies. The cookies received with banner, text or other ads are used by the ad company for targeting purposes only, and we do not have access to this information.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. We can not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you visit a website that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information.
Log Files
Log file information is automatically reported by your browser or mobile device each time you access this website. When you use this website, our servers automatically record certain log file information including the referring site URL, user's IP address, time and date. We use this information to analyze trends and administer the site.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
401khelpcenter.com may revise and update this Privacy Statement at any time by posting such revised Privacy Statement on this website http://www.401khelpcenter.com. By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this privacy statement and to the website Terms of Use for use of this website.
Other Terms of Use
See Terms of Use for use of this website.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:
This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivatives 4.0 International License.
